freevps.us 2012-09-19

# 

    Privacy Policy for freevps.us 
    
    If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin@freevps.us.
    
    Information Collected
    We may collect any or all of the information that via both automated means such as communications profiles and cookies. Personal Information you give us depends on the type of service, support, or sale inqury, and may include your name, address, telephone number, fax number and email address, dates of service provided, types of service provided, payment history, manner of payment, amount of payments, date of payments, domain name, and/or payment information. The financial information will be transferred only be used to bill you for the products and services you purchased.
    
    Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement
    We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about Users upon valid request by government or law officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect your property and rights, or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or stop activity we consider illegal or unethical.
    
    Log Files
    Like many other Web sites, freevps.us makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 
    
    Cookies and Web Beacons 
    freevps.us does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 
    
    DoubleClick DART Cookie 
    .:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on freevps.us.
    .:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to freevps.us and other sites on the Internet. 
    .:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 
    
    These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on freevps.us send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 
    
    freevps.us has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 
    
    You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. freevps.us's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 
    
    If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
    
    <<?
